So there are really two things that you need to keep in mind when you're doing this.
因此，在执行此操作时，您需要牢记两件事。
One is you need to think around the topic and two as you need to be able to ask open questions.
一是您需要围绕主题进行思考，二是您需要能够提出开放性问题。
Not every question is a good question.
不是每个问题都是好问题。
You have to know that First not every question is a good question.
你必须知道，首先不是每个问题都是一个好问题。
If your goal is a good conversation and you can test that by asking those questions and seeing if other
如果您的目标是一次良好的对话，您可以通过提出这些问题并查看是否有其他问题来测试它
people have a lot to say so let's first talk about what some bad questions might be for discussion.
人们有很多话要说，所以让我们先谈谈一些不好的问题可能需要讨论。
So let's say we're talking about smoking in public.
假设我们谈论的是在公共场合吸烟。
This is something people talk about in America.
这是人们在美国谈论的话题。
There are a lot of rules about smoking in public where it can be done where it can't be done.
在公共场所吸烟有很多规定，在不能吸烟的地方可以吸烟。
And these conversations happen.
这些对话发生了。
But let's look at a bad question.
但是让我们看一个不好的问题。
If we're having a good discussion there are good questions and bad questions.
如果我们的讨论很好，就会有好问题和坏问题。
A bad question might be when did smoking first become banned in your city.
一个不好的问题可能是您所在城市何时开始禁止吸烟。
So this is a when question and the answer to this when questioned by the way banned means it became
所以这是一个什么时候的问题，当被禁止的方式质疑时，这个问题的答案意味着它变成了
illegal.
非法的。
The answer to this ban question doesn't really matter to the conversation let's say it's 1998.
这个禁令问题的答案对谈话并不重要，假设是 1998 年。
What can you say after that.
之后还能说什么。
When did smoking become banned in your city.
您所在的城市何时禁止吸烟。
Well either the answer is I don't know or I know it's 1998 with either answer Do you really feel like
好吧，要么答案是我不知道，要么我知道这是 1998 年的任何一个答案 你真的觉得
OK now I have something to say.
好的，现在我有话要说。
No this is not a very good question at all because it doesn't make the other person think of anything.
不，这根本不是一个很好的问题，因为它不会让其他人想到任何事情。
It doesn't make them want to share an opinion.
这不会让他们想要分享意见。
Instead we should focus on saying something that makes the other person want to give their opinion.
相反，我们应该专注于说一些让对方想要发表意见的话。
Because when someone asks for your opinion you probably have a lot to say.
因为当有人询问你的意见时，你可能有很多话要说。
Another example of a bad question is a very basic yes no question like Is Is smoking allowed at the
另一个坏问题的例子是一个非常基本的是不是问题，例如 Is Is Smoke allowed at the
airport.
飞机场。
It's either yes or it's no.
要么是，要么不是。
So we have to be very careful about yes no questions because sometimes yes no questions are just conversation
所以我们必须非常小心是不是问题，因为有时是不是问题只是对话
Enders they sort of end the conversation or they make it hard to continue.
Enders 他们有点结束谈话，或者他们很难继续。
Now sometimes yes no questions work.
现在有时是的，没有问题。
If you said for example do you think smoking should be allowed at airports then someone could say no
例如，如果您说您认为机场应该允许吸烟，那么有人可能会说不
I don't.
我不。
And then you could say why.
然后你可以说出原因。
So asking a do you think question can be really good as long as you follow up with why.
因此，只要您跟进原因，问一个您认为问题是否真的很好。
And then you get there thinking the other person's thinking behind the issue.
然后你就想到了问题背后的其他人的想法。
OK.
好的。
So I think we've made it clear that asking for basic information a fact asking someone to tell you a
所以我认为我们已经明确要求提供基本信息是要求某人告诉你一个事实
fact about something that they may or may not know or asking them to answer a very very basic yes no
关于他们可能知道或可能不知道的事情的事实，或者要求他们回答一个非常基本的是 否
question that these are bad ideas when it comes to actually communicating with another person and having
质疑这些在与他人实际交流和拥有
a good discussion.
一个很好的讨论。
Nothing wrong with those questions.
这些问题没有错。
If you're looking for the answers.
如果你正在寻找答案。
But when you have a discussion you're not looking for the answers really you're looking to engage with
但是，当您进行讨论时，您并不是在寻找真正想要参与的答案
another person to connect with another person.
另一个人与另一个人联系。
So we want to keep our questions open asking how questions asking why questions.
因此，我们希望保持我们的问题开放性，询问如何询问为什么问题。
We'll look at some more examples of the types of questions that we can ask.
我们将看一些我们可以提出的问题类型的更多示例。
But these are more open questions.
但这些都是更开放的问题。
But we also have to think around the topics I want to talk about what that really means to think around
但我们也必须思考我想谈论的话题真正意味着什么
a topic.
一个话题。
Think about a topic as something at the center.
将一个主题视为中心的东西。
So this is at the center.
所以这是在中心。
OK here's here's this thing at the center and this is our topic which is smoking in public.
好的这里'这里是中心的东西，这是我们在公共场所吸烟的话题。
OK.
好的。
What are the things that are related to this connected to this in some way.
与此相关的事物在某种程度上与此相关。
We have to now be able to think in the abstract to think abstractly Well we could directly ask questions
我们现在必须能够抽象地思考才能抽象地思考我们可以直接提问
about smoking in public.
关于在公共场所吸烟。
We could also ask questions about addiction ups HDD addiction right.
我们还可以询问有关上瘾 ups HDD 上瘾的问题。
We could talk about how people are addicted to smoking we could talk about.
我们可以谈论人们是如何对吸烟上瘾的。
We could talk about peer pressure peer pressure is the idea that because all of my friends do something
我们可以谈论同伴压力同伴压力是因为我所有的朋友都做某事的想法
I do something and that might be related to why is it that more men smoke than women.
我做了一些事情，这可能与为什么男性吸烟多于女性有关。
Why is it that in some countries smoking is very popular but in others it isn't.
为什么在一些国家吸烟很受欢迎，而在另一些国家却不是。
We could talk about maybe we could talk about hypotheticals and this is where we just sort of imagine
我们可以谈论也许我们可以谈论假设，这就是我们想象的地方
a situation that may or may not be true let's say for example that in the future medicine is so good
一种情况可能是真的，也可能不是，例如，将来医学会很好
that it's impossible for you to die from heart disease or cancer.
你不可能死于心脏病或癌症。
Does that mean that we should no longer think about smoking.
这是否意味着我们不应该再考虑吸烟了。
What do you think the future would be like in regards to smoking.
你认为未来在吸烟方面会是什么样子。
If we didn't have to worry about heart disease or cancer would smoking still be popular or not.
如果我们不必担心心脏病或癌症，吸烟是否仍然流行。
And then you could ask why is that OK.
然后你可以问为什么这样可以。
So this is maybe an interesting question we could ask lots of these sorts of hypothetical interesting
所以这可能是一个有趣的问题，我们可以问很多这些假设的有趣的问题
imaginary questions in imaginary situations related to the topic of smoking or health or even addiction
与吸烟或健康甚至成瘾主题相关的想象情境中的想象问题
or peer pressure.
或同伴压力。
Maybe another related topic connected to this is about public spaces.
也许与此相关的另一个相关主题是关于公共空间。
How much control should the government have over public spaces.
政府应该对公共空间有多少控制权。
Should the government be able to control everything about what is done in a public space.
政府是否应该能够控制在公共场所所做的一切。
We could of course we could talk about health risks.
我们当然可以谈论健康风险。
Now this one you have to be a little bit careful about because if you just say to the other person could
现在这个你必须要小心一点，因为如果你只是对另一个人说
you please tell me the risks involved with maybe smoking.
请告诉我可能吸烟的风险。
Well it's a little bit obvious right.
好吧，这有点明显。
If you ask someone to tell you what risks are involved with smoking it's kind of just a list of things
如果您要求某人告诉您吸烟会带来哪些风险，那只是清单
well you could get cancer.
好吧，你可能会得癌症。
Well you could get heart disease.
那么你可能会得心脏病。
Well you could get this.
那么你可以得到这个。
Well you could get this and then you're just asking people to know something and then they're just basically
好吧，你可以得到这个，然后你只是要求人们知道一些事情，然后他们基本上就是
telling you the list of things that they know is that really a discussion.
告诉你他们知道的事情的清单真的是一个讨论。
Again focus more on on opinions focus more on getting somebodies idea.
再次更多地关注意见，更多地关注获得某人的想法。
Focus more on getting solutions to problems.
更专注于解决问题。
Right.
正确的。
So if we're talking about the health risks maybe they're obvious but maybe we focus on one specific
因此，如果我们谈论健康风险，也许它们是显而易见的，但也许我们专注于一个特定的
thing maybe we focus on the health risks related to a mother's right.
事情也许我们关注与母亲权利相关的健康风险。
Pregnant women.
孕妇。
And how could we have a space for people to smoke and at the same time make sure that pregnant women
我们怎么能有一个供人们吸烟的空间，同时确保孕妇
are not exposed to what we call second hand second hand smoke.
不会接触到我们所说的二手烟。
Right now we're looking for solutions.
现在我们正在寻找解决方案。
When you ask somebody to give you a good idea about how to solve something a lot of the time people
很多时候，当你请某人给你一个关于如何解决问题的好主意时，人们
will be very interested to share their idea.
将非常有兴趣分享他们的想法。
So all of these things are kind of connected to this idea of smoking in public but they're not exactly
所以所有这些事情都与在公共场合吸烟的想法有关，但并不完全是
only the topic of smoking in public.
只有在公共场合吸烟的话题。
So I just want to give you this thought before we really look at some examples.
所以在我们真正看一些例子之前，我只想给你这个想法。
When you want to have a discussion keep the questions open and your main focus should be to get the
当您想进行讨论时，请保持问题的开放性，您的主要重点应该是获得
other person thinking about something to give an opinion.
其他人在思考某事以发表意见。
To give a solution to give an idea to consider something that's hypothetical which means not real.
给出一个解决方案，给出一个想法来考虑假设的东西，这意味着不真实。
And also don't just stay on that one thing look directly around it in the abstract and think about what
也不要只停留在那一件事上
ideas are related to that topic or that discussion point or whatever it is and then use those related
想法与该主题或该讨论点或其他任何内容有关，然后使用那些相关的
ideas or the topic itself to ask those really interesting questions.
想法或主题本身来问那些真正有趣的问题。
If you get good at this everyone will want to have conversations with you.
如果你擅长这一点，每个人都会想和你交谈。
If you get good at asking good questions then other people will really want to communicate with you
如果你善于提出好问题，那么其他人会很想和你交流
and share their ideas with you and we'll respect you when you're having a discussion it's not about
并与您分享他们的想法，当您进行讨论时我们会尊重您，这不是关于
I'll say my opinion you say your opinion.
我说我的看法，你说你的看法。
It's about listening to what other people say and thinking about how to ask them a great question that
这是关于倾听其他人的意见并思考如何向他们提出一个很好的问题
opens up a completely new idea.
开辟了一个全新的想法。
Whenever I have discussions with people I always try to focus on the questions instead of just giving
每当我与人讨论时，我总是试图专注于问题而不是仅仅给出
my opinions because I find the questions and the answers to those questions.
我的意见，因为我找到了问题和这些问题的答案。
If they're good questions allows me to understand another person more and maybe maybe get a new idea
如果他们是好问题，可以让我更多地了解另一个人，也许会得到一个新的想法
that I never thought about before.
这是我以前从未想过的。